

#### **CONTACT**



+91-7382481437



annamdasuraghuram@gmail.com



10, 18th street, Tansi Nagar, Velacheri, Chennai - 600042

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Java Script
- React JS
- Node JS/ Express JS
- Mongo DB
- Redux

## **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Hindi
- Telugu

## **RAGHU RAM ANNAMDASU**

## MERN STACK DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

An enthusiastic and high-energy driven professional, targeting assignment in Software Development with an organization of repute. M.Tech (Power Systems, IIT-Dhanbad) qualified professional offering around 5 years of experience in Electrical design of Switchgear for Industrial plants.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Design Engineer - M/s L&T Construction
July 2017 - May 2021

Role - Design of electrical system for Effluent treatment plants, Irrigation projects including Large Pumping Plants & Switchyards for Industrial & large water systems.

Senior Proposals Engineer - M/s VA Tech Wabag June 2021 - November 2021

Role - Design of electrical system for Effluent/ Sewage treatment plants, Desalination plants and preparation of bids for tenders adhering specifications and ensuring cost optimization.

Senior Associate Consultant - M/s Infosys November 2021 - May 2022

Role - Design of electrical system for Gas Compressor plants, ensure the completion of all project drawings and supervision of 3d modelling of the project.

# **EDUCATION**

Indian Institute of Technology (IIT), Dhanbad 2015 - 2017

M.Tech (Power Systems Engineering) - 9.1/10 CGPA

Andhra University, Visakhapatnam 2010 - 2014

BE (Electrical & Electronics Engineering) - 9.22/10 CGPA

Board of Intermediate, Andhra Pradesh 2008 - 2010

Intermediate (Maths, Physics & Chemistry) - 96.1%

Board of Secondary Education, AP 2007 - 2008

SSC (10th Standard) - 91.2%